<resources>
	<string name="about_VMAT_Desc">The Vanderbilt Mobile Application Team (or VMAT for
		short) is committed to bringing high quality mobile applications to
		Vanderbilt University (Nashville, TN, USA). We encourage all those
		interested in learning mobile development to join our group. All of
		our work is open source, and can be found at
		http://code.google.com/p/vuphone. We are highly committed to
		developing quality practical applications in a timely manner, and the
		open source, interconnected nature of our development process allows
		an advancement in one application to produce positive effects in many
		others.


		Additionally, our work has multiple implications above and
		beyond general purpose mobile applications to improve quality of life
		at Vanderbilt. Many of our projects transform into cutting edge
		research work as students progress towards a research track. On top of
		research potential, our group trains multiple students in advanced
		mobile development, allowing Vanderbilt to have a ready pool of
		capable developers for various special purpose projects. This group of
		talented individuals helps to increase Vanderbilt's technological advancement and web + mobile presence.

		We currently work with the iPhone and Android platforms, but are always willing to work with new platforms.

		If you are interested in programming for a particular platform, we would be more than happy to have you join our group, and we would help you succeed in any way possible.

		Please contact any of the Faculty Leaders listed on this application if you are interested.
	</string>

	<string-array name="about_developers">
		<item>Kyle Prete (Team Leader)</item>
		<item>Adam Albright</item>
		<item>Kyle Liming</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="student_leaders">
		<item>Hamilton Turner</item>
		<item>Aaron Thompson</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="faculty_leaders">
		<item>Doug Schmidt - d.schmidt@vanderbilt.edu</item>
		<item>Jules White - jules.white@vanderbilt.edu</item>
	</string-array>

	<string-array name="contributors">
		<item>Various Others</item>
	</string-array>	
	
</resources>
